the main difference between
an array and a hash is that a hash
contains
key value pairs each value is
associated with a key so in the example
hash i've created on line one
we have two keys dog and cat
and each of these keys has a string
value
now arrays are a sequence of elements
and each element can be accessed by its
index beginning from zero so
in our example array on line three we
have two elements
the index of fido our first element
would be zero
and the index of fluffy is 1. so to
access a value from our hash
we use the key and
i'll output this value we expect it to
be
fido
and now i'll also access phyto from our
array
using the index and output that as well
you